[
  {
    "question": "what is the best food for pre workout",
    "choice1": "chicken",
    "choice2": "eggs",
    "choice3": "carrot",
    "choice4": "coffee",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question":
      "which the cheapest protien",
    "choice1": "banana",
    "choice2": "eggs",
    "choice3": "soya",
    "choice4": "chicken",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "workouting for which muscle improves testostrone",
    "choice1": "back muscles",
    "choice2": "abs",
    "choice3": "legs",
    "choice4": "shoulders",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question":
      "which fruit contains highest caloires",
    "choice1": "dates",
    "choice2": "apple",
    "choice3": "watermelon",
    "choice4": "jackfruit",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question":
      "what is the best source for complex carbs",
    "choice1": "butter",
    "choice2": "sweet potatoes",
    "choice3": "soya",
    "choice4": "chicken",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question":
      "Best source for simple carbs",
    "choice1": "oil",
    "choice2": "mutton",
    "choice3": "apple",
    "choice4": "sugar",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question":
      "which of the following is a power workout",
    "choice1": "deadlift",
    "choice2": "bicep curls",
    "choice3": "incline dumbble press",
    "choice4": "standing shoulder rises",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question":
      "How can one stay motivated to exercise regularly?",
    "choice1": "vaierty",
    "choice2": "insecurity",
    "choice3": "influencers",
    "choice4": "girls",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question":
      "What are some beginner-friendly exercises for someone just starting their fitness journey?",
    "choice1": "cycling",
    "choice2": "walking",
    "choice3": "hicking",
    "choice4": "planks",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question":
      "How can one improve their flexibility?",
    "choice1": "cardio",
    "choice2": "strength training",
    "choice3": "stretching",
    "choice4": "all the above",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question":
      "Which nutrient is essential for muscle repair and growth after a workout?",
    "choice1": "fiber",
    "choice2": "fat",
    "choice3": "carbs",
    "choice4": "protien",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question":
      "What is the recommended duration of a typical cardio workout session?",
    "choice1": "20mins",
    "choice2": "30mins",
    "choice3": "40mins",
    "choice4": "60mins",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question":
      "Which exercise involves lying on your back and lifting your legs upward while keeping them straight?",
    "choice1": "leg raises",
    "choice2": "squads",
    "choice3": "dynamic lungs",
    "choice4": "seated leg raises",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question":
      "What is the term for the phenomenon where muscles become larger in size due to consistent strength training?",
    "choice1": "endurence training",
    "choice2": "hypertrophy",
    "choice3": "strength training",
    "choice4": "mucatrophy",
    "answer": 2
  }

]